We want to go
back to this idea, to where
this voice in your head
comes from.  And if your friend
says, "Tell me, what did you actually
learn last weekend?"
Then you need to
prepare a little.  You can't just
say, "I can't
remember at all."
This guy said
that this voice in your head, or voices
in your head, is not
you and you have no chance of
influencing what this voice in your
head says if you have ever
suffered from depression or
broken up with a boy or girl.
Then you can't simply
tell your mind to stop
talking about a certain thing.
So, accept
this idea, this notion,
that you cannot influence this person in your
head, and that is
not
you, because these words were spoken
before you could hear them;
because the moment you
hear this word in your head, the
speaker has already disappeared into the
past.  So, where do or did
these voices come from?  They come from
seeds in your
mind.  And as our friend said,
these seeds are planned by you.
And nobody can tell you what to
think in your mind.  It is not
possible.
You can't tell yourself what to
think, and even less so
other
people.  If you have good seeds in your
mind
, this voice will
be fantastic.  She will bring you new ideas
and you will be happy for the rest of your
life.
Um, if you don't learn
to
control this process, then it will simply
continue as it did before this
program started.
And
most are
triggered by these seeds by chance.
They don't even know that they
have seeds, and then the seeds
just open up and they have a
thought in their head and they have
absolutely no control
over it.  Your whole life
, from when you were a child until
now, it's not you who's talking in
your head.  And from now on,
you have the opportunity to decide
what that voice in your head says.
You have this opportunity next week;
you have the opportunity to plant special seeds,
and then your voice will be
wonderful next week
.  It's really nice to live in a head
where the person speaking
is really totally cool and gets better every week.
Once you understand how to
plant this seed, it's like
no other fun that just doesn't stop
and it just keeps
growing.  And
this, uh,
quarter of a million
dollars of this
company, I sold it 25 years ago
.
And that was just the beginning of the
fun.  Since then I've had even
more fun
because I've learned how to
plant the seeds for that voice in
my
head.  And
then he told me, for example, wouldn't
it be cool if we
went to Mexico City again next year?
[Music]
So, what you'll learn this weekend is
how to plant this seed
.
I'll repeat the
steps and if we still have time
[music]
, then I'll give you a
bit of a headache in connection with
the
poem, and if we still
have time after that, then we can do a question
and answer session.  So, if you
already have questions, prepare them
.  We'll go through the pictures now,
because pictures are a good way to
remember things.
I know that P,
Paul, and
Shanti will definitely have a
follow-up program to
explain these pictures again and again.
[Music]
The first one for
$100, we actually have enough money.
[Music]
Okay, for
100. What's happening in this
picture?  So, for $50 you'll pay for what happens in
this picture, and $50 you'll pay for what doesn't
happen in this picture.
[Music]
The woman in this picture planted a seed
and a tree
grew from it.  What does the tree symbolize?
This is the tree, the seeds
she
planted some time ago, so
a tree for her
spirit.  And what doesn't happen in the
picture?  She is not him.
Yes, that's a strange
image, because people remember
strange
images.  People don't remember
normal pictures very well.
And when you think about this weekend
, think about this
picture.  I want to plant a voice
that comes into my mind
and tells me cool things to do
.  For example, the way I
started the diamond business, which was
with
$7, and this person in my mind
was
very much in the diamond business,
we have a special expression.
That means
Nutmck, which means when someone always says "ne ne
nee",
so I constantly had that voice in my
ear.  Make this diamond deal.  Make
this
diamond deal.  And that was
incredible.  The
world's largest jewelry store.  And so if you
develop this voice,
then it's totally funny and you
might also have this
next picture.   Do
we have enough money?  We might have to hitchhike
home
.  So don't raise your hand until you
know.
This image
represents the fact that there are
many options, many
possibilities.  What you learn here
is, uh,
only the
best.  There is, by the way, a special
system.
If he chooses you now, then
you give him $50 afterwards.
The special system
is to plant good ideas for
[music]
.  Instead of the bad
voices.  There are
many, many good voices.  Financial
independence, happiness in the family.
You can choose from different voices
, but I think the
creativity voice
is the best.  This might be that
new idea voice, because
you can then use this voice for all
other voices.  For example, I want
a new
idea.  I might have a new
idea about
how my wife
can do the dishes and do something else at the same time
.  My wife probably
already does that anyway.
And if you are very creative, then
you can be
creative in many different ways
.  And in this
class, we focus
on this
creatively expressive
speaking
voice.  If you smile now,
you can raise your hand
.  Next picture.
[Music]
If you want new ideas, it's
best to go to classes you do
n't understand.
I didn't mean you should go to every
class you don't
understand,
but it's a simple suggestion.  We have
three classes every week and they are
free.
These are the
translation classes that are
difficult, and the difficult things
make you strong.  You might know this
from the gym, from the
fitness studio.  And don't
worry if you don't
understand everything, or if you don't
understand anything at all.  That's not important.  Just sit there
.
And listen
.  Dama
progress.  It doesn't increase quite
gradually
.  It goes down, down,
down.  What?
If you
attend
classes for three weeks, it's just like
meditation.  You meditate, you meditate, you
meditate, then Netflix, Netflix,
Netflix, then more meditation,
meditation, then Netflix, Disney, then more
meditation, meditation.
It's impossible for you to always
go up.  Just don't think about it at all
.
You should
crash once a month.  Your
patience should increase, increase,
increase.  Then
someone comes along in a car and bumps into
you, then you break down and
then it continues with
patience, patience, patience.  Nobody is
perfect.  If you are perfect, then
you don't need to come to this class
.  It's certain that you'll
break down eventually.  So expect it and don't take it too
seriously.
[Music]
Oh no, I forgot to meditate, to
meditate.  Just a calm and moderate
morning.  Next picture.
It's simply
[music]
a
bag, you can
open it and you can put your phone in it
and that helps you avoid using the computer or
iPad
.  If you come with me when
I'm finished
, then I'll give you
[music]
.  There are
some that you
can wear over your shoulder and some that you
can close with a zipper.
And that's my favorite thing, always
living in the
moment.  So if you forget to
come along, that's okay.  No, I'll give
you this one
and hopefully I'll get another one
.
[Music]
answers, that is related to the last picture
.
To
experience
what happened in the garden
, do you have to
pack away all your devices, all your things for 8 hours?  Your
computer and mobile phone.  That's the wrong
answer, but it's a good answer.
$100.
Before I started this Goodnight
Book Club, I had
stopped reading books, I mean real books,
and I just had all the books
on my
phone, but I still enjoyed
reading before falling asleep
.  But if I read on my phone
before falling asleep, then I don't sleep
well either.  If I read a proper
book for about 15 minutes before I
fall asleep, then I sleep well.
And
sometimes from 10 to
6, when I
'm traveling and alone in my
hotel room, which is a
very
dangerous word
because I don't set my timer then
,
I always ask to
receive a message at 10 o'clock
and then
I put away the computer and
the phone
, but then I still have
the remote control for the TV in the
hotel.
[Music]
Sometimes the hotel has two,
if I've handed one in
.  If you maintain this system
, your
productivity will double.
Saint
Lur didn't say you could either have
great eye candy or sleep for 8 hours
.  I believe that a woman who
has slept for 5 hours and
uses a lot of Laurent does not look as good as
a woman who has slept for 8 hours
.  It looks more natural after 8
hours of sleep and is the
cheapest makeup.
What is the name of this store?
Sephora.  Tell you men, if the
women want to go to Sephora, then do
n't go.  You won't get out of there for less than $300
if you go to the drugstore.  Go
to DMKT or something like that, they have the
same lipstick for only
€2.  So come up with an apology
.
So, it changes your face and
makes your mind powerful.
You can make twice as much money
and you'll never know it because you've
never
tried.  I'm not saying that
one night with 8 hours of sleep
makes a difference.
If you do it for three weeks
, your mind will become stronger
and you will feel
healthier.  I am the
grandfather.  I go to
yoga class and there are all these
20-year-olds there and I always think,
wow, you need to
get some sleep and put away your stupid
phones
.
16 hours a day is enough, then
take 8 hours for yourself.  Give the phone
16 hours, but accept that the phone is supposed to
give you time, but it costs you time.
So please, please,
please, if
you don't have the strength to do it
yourself, then ask your
friend.  I have a friend who
lives right next door, 2 minutes away from
me, because my wife is on vacation or
something.
Then at 10 o'clock he comes over and
extends his hand.
So find a
friend, if you're like
me, then you might not have the
strength to do it yourself and you
need friends to
help you.  The phone does something similar,
is very similar to
alcohol.  We are all addicted.
Where do you like to read and look at
your phone the most?  I'm in a
certain room and on a certain
seat, and I'm looking around,
and after an hour my
wife knocks on the door and says, "Well, other
people, other people, they also have to go
to the toilet here."
And then I say, "Oh, I'm sorry, there's
such interesting news
about
Trump right now."  So, be careful.  If you do
n't have the strength yourself, ask your
friend and help
each other.  You won't
regret it.  You will be a much more
successful person.   Please
.
I think
McDonald's, Kentucky Fried
Chicken and so on are going to
kill me.  If that happens, then
you'll know
why.  Next
picture.
I like to have several, um, real
paper books with me when I
fall asleep.  Sometimes I feel like
I
could read something a little more profound [music].  Then maybe I'll read the
Diamond Cutter
book, the business book.
And sometimes I'm so
tired,
then I'd rather do something like the garden.
So maybe you just have two
books next to the bed.  One that
is a bit more in-depth and one that
is a bit more relaxing.
If
you read this book, you will fall
into a deep sleep within 6 minutes,
and even if you read it in the morning
, you will fall into a deep sleep after 6 minutes
.  I did
not show this picture.  I was supposed to
show that yesterday, but I didn't.
And that's the
last one from
yesterday, and I told you that there is
a specific method to
plant the seeds for the inner voice.
And this guy here, he's doing that
right now
[music]
Which, so you think, what seed did
I plant to make this
happen?  This class, these three
days are
fun.  Why?
Geschilla didn't teach you a new meditation
where you feel more guilty
than last week, because if you do
n't do that, everyone
likes to feel guilty after all.  Me
too.  I
once had a student who said, "
Gesha, please don't teach me a new
meditation."  And I said,
why?   That was
already bad for me, because I don't
do any of the things you've taught me so
far, the things you've taught me in the past
.  Now you're going to teach me another one
.  No.  And this,
you can do anywhere and nobody
will even notice that you're
meditating.  Perhaps someone thinks they are
thinking about some woman right now.
But he doesn't.  He
thinks, he thinks, what seed did I
plant to meet this guy
?  I had a good day.  I
was driving to work
and then the radio was playing Jimmy
Hendrick and I
was so
happy and
then a car
cut me off and at that moment
your
meditation machine meditation about the
creative you
determine.  What kind of seed have I
planted for this
idiot?  Just think about it
.
Then you drive to work, get out of the car
and forget about the
whole thing.  A short, one-minute
meditation.  Three times a day, five times a
day.
When should I
meditate?  Meditate when
something bad
happens and meditate when something
great
happens.  Wow, I
met the most incredible people in
Mexico City.
They were so great.
What have I done?
What are your triggers for meditation, so to speak
?  Will something bad happen,
or will something good happen?
And then you say, why
me?  My teacher taught me everything in a sometimes
strange way, all
day long
.  Even when I cleaned the toilet,
I
learned something.  He bought a television.
and
said, I am the boss in the monastery, I
can watch television, you can't and you are
not allowed to watch television either.  And
then he said, but
if anything interesting
happens on television, then then then
I'll ring the bell.  Ever
wondered why llamas have a bell
?  And he
said, if you hear the bell, then
come running upstairs, because something
interesting is happening on the
phone.  And I said, yes, yes, yes.  And
I was
working near the stairs the whole time, and
then ding ding ding, then I
ran up them.  Then he said, "Look at
the news."
Then there were news reports about a
woman whose house had
burned down, because she
had left the iron on and the
house burned down,
and she cried
and said, "Why me?"
It happens to a lot of people that they
leave their irons on, but why did
my house burn down?  And then
he said, okay, you can go.
And I thought, uh,
why?  And he said,
go. Then I continued
working and then it went ding, ding ding again
.  After an hour I
ran back upstairs and then he said,
look at this.  And then this handsome
presenter, uh, knocked on
the door in a
rough part of New
York, and a poor woman opened it,
and he said,
he then said to her, "You've
won the lottery."  Here's a check
for 5 million
dollars and they love showing it on
TV, how she freaks out and
screams
and dances
around to [music].  He
asked me what she didn't say or
ask, why
me, if you win the lottery
.
No one asks why me?
But if your house
burns down, then why me? Why me?
If you
're on the creative voice team, then
you should be asking yourself why me all the time.
When something stupid happens, it's
natural that you'd say, "Why me?"
But even if something good
happens, then I asked why
I
[music]
By the way, did you notice that I did
n't tell you
what to think, but
you should only
ask yourself the question and
how you answer it, that's your
problem.
I ask you only to ask yourselves the question
.  If something good
happens, if something bad happens,
why
not?  And you'll find out for yourself.   Do
n't believe that this will last longer than 2
days
in your
life.  Your life moves very
fast.  You don't have time to spend two
hours thinking about why
some [ __ ] on the
road who took your right of way hit you.
But you can think about it for 30 seconds
.  You know the seeds in
your mind better.  I don't know her
.  So let's get back to
serious
money.  Oh, the money's all gone.
Okay, then you don't need to
pay attention anymore.
[Laughter]
So, why
me?
I've
gone through the documents again and there are
various parts here in the
reading materials, and I
want you to get a feel
for them
.  I read the
Tibetan music, which only
brings happiness [music].  Do that.
Okay.
He is the best
Tibetan music teacher.  And he gives
a free class every week.
So, if you don't come to his class
, you're
crazy.  It's free.  It's
fun and he teaches people how to
read very quickly.
The chair chair.  Bring back the
chair.  OK.  Here is the translation.
Here is the translation.
On the one hand, you have
someone who
is born into their
mother, who on the other hand
continues in a
form that is unchanging.
If this is a pen in itself
, then it will never change.
He will
never stop
writing.  If the pen draws from within
itself
, it will never run dry
.  If the pen comes from me,
from my
seeds, then every time
I
use it, every time I use the pen
, then the ink will be a little
less.  It's not really that the
ink decreases, but rather that the seeds
consume the seeds.
We'll make another one and you
explain to my
wife why.  A big
question: when you write with a pen,
where does the
writing come from?
The writing comes from my seeds.
[Music]
People say the pen exists on its
own
and I say why and they say then
look, it can write on paper
.  But writing does
n't come from the pen.
When you move the ship
, your
mind makes the marks on the paper.  Now there's
bad news.
Why?
Every single minute of the next movie
you watch, where does that come from
?  From which direction?
Oh, I saw Wolverine
and
the new hit movie, or
Deadpool.  By the way, with my
meditation system you can meditate
and watch the film, and then you might wonder
why that's so stupid?
What have I
done?  But who wrote the film
?   You
.  New images appear every minute.  Your
mind creates these
images, and then things
age.  Why?
With some movies, you might be so
glad when it's over
.  I felt I had to
watch it to the end because I had
paid a considerable amount of money
.  And then I tell my wife,
when it's over, I'm so glad it's over
.
But why?  Because your sperm
are running out, and the sperm for your
body will eventually run out too
.  Your
body originated in your
mother through sperm.
First, the
chakras formed, then the energy channels,
then the bones formed
around the energy channels, and then the
muscles formed around the
bones during all those
weeks in your mother's womb.
And every week, uh, there's a new
chakra, and eventually you're
finished and they all come out of the seeds
.  And while you're using your
body
,
when the pen comes out of itself
, then there's absolutely
no reason.  why it
should eventually run out of power.
So, if the pen
comes out of itself, then it will never run out of ink
.  If
the film isn't yours,
then it will go on forever.  But
if he comes from your seed,
then he will eventually grow
old
.  This
question World has certainly got all the money
he has won in the past,
your past
.  This book, in the
poem, is a discussion.  A
dispute between two people, the
angel and the
devil.
Sometimes the angel speaks, and sometimes
the devil speaks.
And
who is
saying this section now, and
why?
She says the angel
[music]
speaks because she explains why you are getting old
.
why the last relationship failed,
and it's good
advice, and therefore it must be the angel
.  We'll do two more and then
we can move on to the questions.
is the second-best bassist in this room.
ngotang miwangutang
ngikotang
gulasok ngikang
[Music]
And so it would also be
completely
irrelevant to even have a thought
where we would
consider a thing as ours
, because none of these
things would ever be my
head, my
mount, my
nose tip, my
eyes that are my eyes, my sense of
sight, my body,
my
physique, and so
on.  If all these things do
not result from things, from seeds, then
none
of them can be mine.  Not even your
mouth or your nose can be yours
.  Your stomach cannot be your stomach
.  Your house cannot be your house
.
A man, your wife, or your
children cannot be yours unless they
result from sperm.  Things that do not result from seeds
can never
be yours.  Things that don't come from seeds
be yours.  And now it gets very
profound.
Things that cannot result from seeds are
not connected to
other
things.
If I say, "My is my
grandson," then
you're saying there's a relationship with this
child, but if there are no ladies,
then there can't be a relationship
.  If Myre comes from within himself
, then he cannot come from
his mother
.  He cannot be from his mother
.  Only things that come from seeds
can also come from other people
.  If the pen comes from within itself
, then I could
never
possess it, because it doesn't come from
my
seed.  The compound also ends up in
semen.  If I lose the relationship,
it will affect my
sperm.  If things don't result from seeds
, they will never age
.  If things don't come from seeds
, nobody can
have them.  You need to think about that
[music]
.  A world that does not
originate from seeds is impossible.
A pen that doesn't come from seed
can never run out of ink
.  You can't
buy a pen that doesn't
contain seeds.  Sometimes you need a pen
and your friend gives you
one.  Sometimes you need a pen
and you go to the store and they say,
sorry, we don't have any more.
You can't get pens in the store
.  You get them from the
seeds.  You must share everything you
have, then you will receive more.
Jesus said this repeatedly
.  Jesus was a pretty
cool master when it came to
seeds.  Give what you want to someone else
.
If someone's
sweater looks good on you,
try to get their phone number
and ask them, "Hey, do
you need my
coat too?"  If someone slaps you on the left
cheek, you say, "Oh, this one,
the right cheek is fine too."
Only a master of seeds speaks
.  Do we even have enough
petrol to get
home?  Who
wrote these verses
?  But what I mean here is,
is that the angel or the devil?
And
why the angel?
But you should never answer a question with another
question, but
with trust.
Angel, because the angel comes from my seed
.  Think of this picture with this
woman.  If you're talking about seeds, then it must
be the angel, because
the
devil doesn't like to talk about seeds.
[Music]
last.  Maybe
Gibson can come here.  A very good
translator from Taiwan.   I have no
idea what he's doing here in Mexico City
.
[Music]
And I'd also like to welcome Emily.
Be called.   Their
specialty
is
women's paperback books.  He has already
completed two, and they are approximately 600 years
old.  And the idea is that you
always have a little book like this with you
, something you always
have in your pocket.
Word translations.  Tim's
translations are good if you're having a
fight with your
husband.
Very
heavy large
books,
but Gebsen's
specialty is these
small ones, i.e., these
paperbacks.  He starts now, after two
he starts with the third.
Let's go.
Incidentally, he helped for many years
on the fundraising team
in
Guadhara to help refugees traveling
between
Central America and the
American border.
There's
a house there now where people can shower
, relax,
eat, and
then get back on the
train, and they've supported that for 10 years
.
[Music]
I'm not going to ask you now
, but in
Taiwan there's
this
box and they're passing it around
and people are putting
change in it and
that has helped with the financing
and now it's also being translated into Spanish
.
more than you.
Thank
you.  OK.
in Spanish
and we
have minutes.
We have 2
minutes.  Guide the
people, take them by the hand and
lead them to absolute
nothingness.  Teach them
not to think, not to think about anything at all.
Let me briefly
explain: if you
want to join the Latin American teaching team, talk to
Aldo
and then you can say so.  What are
you going to do in Costa Rica?  What do
you teach?
Oh, we take the hand of the people
and we guide them, we lead them into
nothingness, and then we teach them
a special meditation
.  Think of
nothing,
then we will teach them when they
meditate.  Think as much as you
can and then they will become true
meditation masters.
Who is speaking to you?
K
the
Devil is
Diablo Diablo.
nice.
[Laughter]
People ask me, Gesch, you have
n't come to Mexico City in so long,
and then they ask me, why did
you come back?
which
reminds me.
When I saw the great cathedral that
day, I became very
religious and
wanted to go to the cathedral
[music]
.  Thank you very much and see you
next year.  M.